Guide to the David McAllester Papers, 1940 - 1996
David McAllester Papers, 1940 - 1996
Special Collections and Archives, Wesleyan University
McAllester, David Park, 1916-
2002-18
7.0
20
David Park McAllester was professor of Anthropology and Music at Wesleyan University from 1947 to 1986. He studied and wrote about the rites and ceremonies of the Navajo Indians and was a co-founder of the Society for Ethnomusicology.
This collection contains drafts of published and unpublished writings, extensive correspondence, field notes and one nineteenth century family photograph album.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisitions Information
Collection donated by David McAllester of Monterey, MA, May 3, 2002.
Biographical Note
David Park McAllester was born in 1916, the youngest of four children. He grew up in Everett, Massachusetts, where he often accompanied his mother on natural history walks as she collected material for her weekly column in the Boston Sunday Herald. Professor McAllester traces his ultimate career as a specialist in Native American culture to an early exposure to reading animal tracks in the snow as well as to the literature of Ernest Thompson Seton, Bret Harte, James Fenimore Cooper and Henry David Thoreau. He was also musical; he sang as a boy soprano beginning around the age of eight and attended private voice lessons with the original intention of becoming a professional singer.
David McAllester attended Harvard University, entering in 1934 and graduating in 1938. There he continued his dual interests in anthropology and music. He took classes in southwestern ethnology and linguistics with Clyde Kluckhohn and sang as a soloist with the Harvard Glee Club. Music led him to his future wife, Susan Watkins, during a joint performance with the Radcliffe Choral Society. After graduating from Harvard, he started at Juilliard; however, he continued to do field work during the summers at an archaeological dig at the Lindenmeier site in Colorado, an activity he had started while at Harvard. He also started taking classes at Columbia University, notably George Herzog's "Primitive Music" class. By the spring of 1940 he had made the decision not to pursue music as a career and had started in the PhD program in anthropology at Columbia with a focus on American Indian music. In the summer of 1940 he joined a linguistic field study of the Comanche in Oklahoma where he did research on peyote songs and rituals. With the war looming, he and Susan were married in September 1940. He spent academic year 1940-1941 at Columbia where he met such luminaries as Franz Boaz and Margaret Mead.
Although not raised in the Quaker tradition, David McAllester had deeply felt pacifist beliefs and joined the 15th Street Meeting of the Society of Friends while living in New York City. With the entry of the United States into World War II he filed for, and was granted, conscientious objector status. He spent the next two years working with the Civilian Public Service (CPS) in a forestry camp in Cooperstown, NY, and the following two years working with the CPS at the Connecticut State Hospital in Middletown, CT.
When the war ended in 1945 he returned to Columbia where he began work on his dissertation on peyote songs. He had a part-time job in the Archive of Primitive Music there and supplemented this with adjunct teaching at Brooklyn College. He was awarded his PhD from Columbia University in 1950. In 1947 he was invited to join the faculty at Wesleyan University where he remained until his retirement in 1986.
Professor McAllester has been active in the development of the field of Ethnomusicology. When he first came to Wesleyan he had a joint appointment in Psychology and Biology. In 1952, at the American Anthropological Association meeting in Philadelphia, he was introduced to Alan Merriam by Willard Rhodes of Columbia University. These three joined forces with Charles Seeger to create a newsletter focused on ethnomusicology, first published in December 1953. The four men founded the Society for Ethnomusicology in 1955. David McAllester broadened the music curriculum at Wesleyan to include non-European music in 1956 with his course Music 31, Ethnic and Folk Music. The World Music Archives at Wesleyan University developed out of the field recordings of Native American ceremonies that he made in the 1940s and '50s, and it was partly his influence that led to the establishment of the department of Anthropology at Wesleyan in 1967. He was appointed professor of Anthropology and Music in 1972.
Professor McAllester traveled extensively during the course of his professional career. He received a Guggenheim grant in 1957 and spent a year in Arizona studying the Navajo Blessingway ritual. In 1960 he was Carnegie visiting professor at the University of Hawaii. In 1972 he spent a sabbatical visiting Japan, Indonesia, India and Finland. In 1978 he taught as a visiting scholar at the University of Queensland, Australia, as a recipient of the Fulbright-Hays Award. His recordings of Comanche and Navajo music led to the establishment of the World Music Archives at Wesleyan University in 1953. This has grown extensively since then with contributions by Professor McAllester and his colleagues.
Beginning in 1979, Professor McAllester taught one full semester per year at Wesleyan, spending the remaining eight months at his home in the Berkshires. He retired fully in 1986. Since then he has continued to be involved in the Society for Ethnomusicology, writing professional book reviews, and has been very involved in his local newspaper.
Collection Overview
The David McAllester collection documents McAllester's interests in writing, research, music and ritual. Early folders in Series I: Writings, feature short stories and poetry which he submitted for consideration to magazines like The New Yorker. David McAllester also published widely, in scholarly journals, book reviews, encyclopedias of music, and materials for teachers. Drafts of his work and correspondence relating to his writings are contained in Series I.
The bulk of David McAllester's professional life consisted of his long tenure at Wesleyan University. Series II contains field notes and an exhaustive correspondence with colleagues in the fields of anthropology and ethnomusicology. Professor McAllester had close relationships with members of the Navajo Nation whom he worked with during field research. He was interested in the ceremonies of the Navajo people, and did extensive work on the Blessingway healing ceremony. He also had close ties to members of the academic world who either acted as a mentor to him, such as Lee Wyman, or whom he mentored, such as Charlotte Frisbie. His field work was an attempt to understand the differences and find the commonalities between people through music and ritual.
The circle of people in his life expanded ever outward and he kept in touch by voluminous letter writing as evidenced in Series III, Correspondence. This series contains both professional and personal letters since David McAllester never clearly drew the line between the two. In all of his correspondence, he kept carbons of letters he wrote, so the collection is easy to follow and rich in detail.
As a young man at the beginning of his career, his studies in anthropology at Columbia were interrupted by World War II. Documents in the beginning of Series IV, Personal History, show his application for Conscientious Objector status and the activities he was involved in during the four years he was in the Civilian Public Service (CPS). Projects of interest to him after formal retirement in 1986 are found in the second half of this series. His writing and administrative talents were put to use for the Monterey News, a local newspaper, for ten years. His humanism shows itself again in his involvement with the Never Again Campaign, a project between the US and Japan to promote understanding and the prevention of the use of nuclear weapons.
David McAllester was married to his wife Susan from 1940 until her death in 1996. Series V contains letters she wrote to him, correspondence of her own with friends, and papers surrounding her final illness.
Series VI consists of a photograph album, circa 1894 from the family of David McAllester's mother, Maude Helen Park McAllester. The photographs are portraits of family members, individually and in groups. Some are labeled with names. They are mostly tintypes.
Collection Arrangement
Series I: Writings, 1943-1995
Series II: Subject area, research and correspondence, 1946-1996
Series III: Correspondence, 1940-1996
Series IV: Personal history, 1941-1996
Series V: Susan McAllester, 1944-1994
Series VI: Photo album, circa 1894
Online Catalog Headings
These and related materials may be found under the following headings in online catalogs.
Blessingway (Navajo rite); Cultural property--Repatriation.; Ethnomusicology.; Frisbie, Charlotte Johnson.; Indians of North America--Music.; McAllester, David Park, 1916-; Mitchell, Frank, 1881-1967.; Navajo Indians--Music.; Navajo Indians--Religion and mythology.; Navajo Indians--Rites and ceremonies.; Peyote songs.; Wesleyan University--Faculty.; World War, 1939-1945--Conscientious objectors.; Wyman, Leland Clifton, 1897-
Related Material
World Music Archives at Wesleyan University has many recordings made by David McAllester. Listening copies are available although a few recordings require Professor McAllester's permission for listening.
World Music Archives also has approximately six linear feet of transcriptions of chants and field notes, un-cataloged.
Blessingway film (3 reels), in Special Collections & Archives. Access restricted. Please contact SC&A staff for information.
Separated Material
Books removed from the David McAllester Papers to be cataloged separately:
1. The comprehensive and self-interpreting family Bible and biblical library combined. 1870
2. Holy Bible. 1833
3. Cochrane, W.R. history of the town of Antrim, New Hampshire. 1880
4. Geoffrey, Theodate. An immigrant in Japan, Boston and New York. 1926
5. Suckanesset: wherein may be read a history of Falmouth, Massachusetts. 1930
6. Morrison, Leonard Allison. The history of the Morison or Morrison family…1880
7. The history of Windham in New Hampshire, 1719-1883. 1883
8. Prescott, William. The Prescott memorial…1870
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Series I: Writings, 1943-1995
  This series is arranged chronologically. It traces David McAllester's writings from early short stories and poetry to scholarly journal articles, book reviews and books. The last four folders contain notes for columns for the newspaper Monterey News.
  - Juvenile Writing, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Early stories 1., undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Early stories 2., undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Early writings, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Slim Boy, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Turquoise Horse, 1952-53 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Writings submitted for publication, 1943-48 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Book reviews and articles, 1950-59 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Book reviews and articles, 1960-67 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Book reviews and articles, 1968-69 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Reprints, 1960s (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Book reviews and articles, 1970-78 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Reprints, 1970s (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Book reviews and articles, 1980-82 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Book reviews and articles, 1983-89 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Reprints, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Book reviews and articles, 1991-95 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Undated writings, CV and list of publications, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Monterey News, poetry, 1990-91 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Monterey News,"Who's Who in Monterey", 1990s (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Monterey News, Wildlife Survey, 1991-94 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Monterey News, Wildlife Survey, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Series II: Subject area, research and correspondence, 1946-1996
  This series contains field notes and correspondence with colleagues in the fields of anthropology and ethnomusicology. It also contains notes for courses and talks given by David McAllester in the United States and abroad. It is arranged alphabetically by topic.
  - A Hilo Wau, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Newspaper clipping on a federal case involving definition of the uli'uli and whether it is a musical instrument or not.
  - American Indian Archaeological Institute, 1987-89 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Bibliography for Robbins Swamp Project ('82-'88). Research program summer '87-fall '88.
  - Anthropology, 1965-68 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Correspondence relevant to anthropology.
  - Australia, 1974-79 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, timetable, extensive handwritten notes for course taught in Australia summer 1978.
  - Blessingway Film, 1957-64 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Correspondence and notes on Blessingway film from its conception to creation.
  - Blessingway texts, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Texts of Blessingway chants.
  - Blessingway, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    25 pages of handwritten notes transcribing interview (with father of Frank Mitchell)?
  - Brown, Bob, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Correspondence with Bob Brown while he was in India.
  - Brown University, 1988-97 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Brown University: seminars in ethnomusicology taught fall '89 and spring 1990.
  - Burrows, David, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Galley proofs of Burrows' "Sound, Speech, and Music" Amherst: U Mass Press, 1990. Notes by DM.
  - Cacioppo, Curt, 1982-85 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Curt Cacioppo, composer/pianist. Snake Dance Trio score for flute, cello and piano. Two other compostitions as well.
  - Chinle, AZ, 1963-68 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Correspondence with Irene Mitchell and family.
  - Chinle, AZ, 1982-99 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Coley, Kathleen, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Paper by K. Coley. Editorial marks by David McAllester. His notes in front: list of names with symbols.
  - Correspondence, 1973-74 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Professional correspondence.
  - Correspondence, 1975-76 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1980-85 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Dawn Songs 1., 1963 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Musical notations of 12 dawn songs/transcriptions of words plus 'Johnson's guide' (Frisbie). Some notes by D McA.
  - Dawn Songs 2., undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    27 dawn songs attributed to Ray Winne, notated with words. Extensive handwritten notes by D McA.
  - Dawn Songs 3., undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Dawn songs 1-9 (missing #5) attributed to Smith. Accompanying notes by D McA.
  - de Laguna, Frederica, 1966-68 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Frederica de Laguna, Bryn Mawr, PA. Correspondece.
  - Ethnomusicology, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Correspondence.
  - Ethnomusicology, 1974-78 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Field study, 1950-52 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Proposal for field study. Related subject materials.
  - First Snake Song, Coyote's Song, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Songs of Ray Winnie Lukachukai, transposed, notated and words transcribed.
  - Frisbie, Charlotte, 1978-85 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Correspondence with Charlotte Frisbie, especially regarding book in honor of Lee Wyman.
  - Grove's Dictionary, 1982-85 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Correspondence and contracts for entries to Groves made by D McA.
  - Hinton, Leanne, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Thesis by Leanne Hinton.
  - House songs, 1950, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    38 pages of handwritten notes on hogan (house) songs. Six pages of typed translations and notes.
  - Interviews, Ramah, NM, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Field study. Research interviews with 5 people in Ramah, NM. Questions about their songs and instruments.
  - Isaacs, Tony, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Project report for seminar in ethnomusicology 5/26/65.
  - Kavasch, Barrie, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Miscellaneous articles and leaflets on plants in American Indian life.
  - Kelsey, John Russell, 1983-93 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    John Russell Kelsey, correspondence.
  - Kudyapi, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Photos taken of the musical instrument (kudyapi), in the Philippines.
  - Lichtenfeld, Danny, 1993-94 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Two papers and bibliography by Danny Lichtenfeld.
  - Maps, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Miscellaneous maps.
  - Matthews, Washington, c1992 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Correspondence w/ Wheelwright Museum re: Matthews' wax cylinder recordings of Navajo music made early 1890's.
  - Matthews, Washington, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
    "The Treatment of Ailing Gods" manuscript in the W. Matthews collection now in MNCA, Santa Fe, NM. 2 copies.
  - Mitchell, Frank, 1974-80 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    "Navajo Blessingway Singer: The Autobiography of Frank Mitchell, 1881-1967". Photographs of Mr. Mitchell.
  - Navajo poems, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Essay concerning 5 different translations of the same Navajo poem.
  - Navajo specialists, museums, etc., 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Navajo specialists, museums, etc., 1969-71 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Navajo specialists, museums, etc., 1972-79 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Navajo Studies Conference, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Navajo Studies Conference, Feb. 20-22, 1986. Albuquerque, NM.
  - New Indian Music, 1975-76 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - New Indian Music, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Field Notes I.
  - New Indian Music, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Field Notes II.
  - New Indian Music, 1975-77 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Newspaper clippings mostly from Navajo Times, some correspondence, all relating to new Indian music.
  - New Indians: Brigham Young University, 1982-83 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Sessions given at the American Indian National Self-Reliance Conference at Brigham Young University, March 9-11, 1983.
  - Olin, Caroline, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Olin, Caroline B. "Early Navajo Sandpainting Symbols in Old Navajoland: Visual Aspects of Mythic Images". Autographed
  - Past jobs I., bulk 1950-65 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Correspondence re: guest lectures, symposia, etc.
  - Past jobs II., 1980-88 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Past jobs II., 1980-88 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Paul, Maggie, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Correspondence re: recordings of Eastern woodlands native American music recorded by D McA in 1952.
  - Pequot, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Correspondence with Pequot tribe re:plans for archives for Eastern North American music at the Pequot Museum.
  - Peyote research, 1946-47 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Correspondence relevant to PhD thesis on peyote songs.
  - Peyote controversy, 1951-56 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Newspaper clippings, writings and correspondence.
  - Peyote paper, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Handwritten notes for paper.
  - Religious Character of Native American Humanities, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Correspondence and notes for paper given at conference at Arizona State University, April 14-16, 1977.
  - Repatriation, bulk 1992-94 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Correspondence re: repatriation of recordings of Navajo music made by DMcA. Transcription of interview, Jan 1993.
  - Roberts, Helen, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Bibliography of works by H. Roberts, chronology.
  - Sacred Mountain Foundation, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Legal paperwork establishing a Massachusetts chapter of this foundation.
  - Saumaiwai, Chris, 1981-82 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Chris Saumaiwai. Music of Fiji.
  - Sligo Rover, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Janet Whittle, Masters Thesis "The Sligo Rover": copy of paper and correspondence.
  - Smith, Albert, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Interview with Albert Smith of Navajo Nation. Handwritten field notes, typed notes. Story extracted and typed separately.
  - Stafford, Evalyn and Gordon, 1987-89 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Stafford, Evalyn and Gordon, 1990-92 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Swing, Pamela, 1978-83 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Correspondence with and student papers by Pamela Swing (incl. "Musical Toys in the Alexander Lazar Collection").
  - Tokyo, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    4th International Symposium of the Conservation and Restoration of Cultural Property, Tokyo, August 6-9, 1980.
  - Tumaco, Columbia, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Transcripts of interviews done in Tumaco, Columbia by Tom _? Pages 1009-1132 plus one page appendix.
  - World Music Program, history, 1964-75 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Documentation, correspondence regarding establishment of World Music Program 1963.
  - Worlds of Music, 1983-2000 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Correspondence regarding publication of "Worlds of Music" edited by J. Titon, Schirmer Books.
  - Wyman, Lee, 1961-80 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Extensive correspondence with Lee Wyman, colleague and mentor. Scholar in Navajo studies.
  - Wyman, Lee, 1981-87 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Wyman estate, 1980-81, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Legal correspondence relating to estates of Lee Wyman and his wife.
- Series III: Correspondence,1940-1996
  The correspondence in this series is arranged chronologically. Letters include carbon copies of letters sent by David McAllester as well as letters received by him. Correspondents include family, friends and colleagues.
  - 1940 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 1941 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 1942 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 1943 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 1944 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 1945 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 1946 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 1948 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - 1949 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - undated, 1940s (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - 1950 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - 1951 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - 1952 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - 1953 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - 1954 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - 1955 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - 1956 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - 1957 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - 1958 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - 1959 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - undated, 1950s (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 1960 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - 1961 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 1962 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - 1963 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 1964 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 1965 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 1966 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - 1967 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - 1968 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - 1969, Jan-Apr (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - 1969, May-Dec (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - undated, 1960s (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - 1970 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - 1971 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - 1972 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - 1973 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - 1974 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - 1975 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - 1976 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - 1977, Jan-Mar (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - 1977, Apr-Dec (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - 1978 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 1979 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - 1980 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - 1981 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - 1982 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - 1983 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - 1984 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - 1985 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - 1986 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - 1987 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - 1988 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - 1989 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - undated, '70s and '80s (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - undated, '70s and '80s (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - undated, '70s and '80s (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - 1990 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - 1991 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - 1992 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - 1993 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - 1994 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - 1995 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - 1996 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - undated, 1990s (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Series IV: Personal History, 1941-1996
  This series brackets David McAllester's professional life. It documents his time spent in the Civilian Public Service as a conscientious objector during World War II. This series also documents his activities during his retirement from 1986 to the present. Arrangement of this series is chronological.
  - Conscientious Objector, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Application for CO status.
  - Cooperstown, NY, 1941-42 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, minutes of inter-camp meetings.
  - Cooperstown, Camp Paper, 1941-43 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Newsletter of Civilian Public Service (CPS) #12.
  - Status of CPS #81, 1943-46 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Correspondence: withdrawal of CPS#81 from AFSC administration.
  - Epistles, Reporters et al., 1943-45 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    Newsletters/bulletins for CPS #81.
  - Epistles, file copies, 1943-44 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    Complete sets of newsletters for CPS #81.